Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
Subtitles by explosiveskull & EVO
Sync by GoldenBeard
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(TICKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Excommunicado.
In effect. 6:00 p.m..
Eastern Standard Time.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
CHARON: I do hope
that Mr. Wick
finds his way to safety.
He knew the rules.
he broke them.
And killed a man
on company grounds. Charon.
Do you expect him
to make it out?
$14 million bounty
on his head.
And every interested party in
this city wants a piece of it.
I'd say the odds
are about even.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(MEN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: You think the hospital's
there to help. man?
(LAUGHING) No way!
They'll kill you just as soon
as they'll make you better!
(LAUGHS)
But I know better. man.
I know better.
I know what I'm...
Tick tock. Mr. Wick.
Tick tock.
Tick tock. Tick... (LAUGHING)
No time to dilly-dally.
Mr. Wick!
(HORNS HONKING)
The New York Public Library.
You got it.
(HORNS BLARING)
(HORNS CONTINUE BLARING)
Change of plan.
To the Continental.
Can you see that he's received
by the concierge?
Yes. sir. Mr. Wick.
Good dog. Good dog.
(HORNS CONTINUE BLARING)
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Excommunicado.
In effect. 20 minutes.
(A CAPPELLA SINGERS
SINGING)
(JOHN PANTING)
Can I help you?
Russian Folktale.
Alexander Afanasyev.
- (KEYBOARD CLACKING)
- (SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
1864.
(PEN SCRATCHING ON PAPER)
- Level two.
- Thank you.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
ERNEST:
"Consider your origins.
"You were not made
to live as brutes.
"but to follow virtue
and knowledge."
(CLOSES BOOK)
Dante.
Looking a little
run down there. John.
Ernest. I still have time.
It's almost up. Who's gonna
know the difference?
You sure this is what
you wanna do?
Fourteen million.
It's a lot of money.
Not if you can't spend it.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(JOHN GROANS)
(GROANING)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GRUNTING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SHUSHES)
(GRUNTING)
JOHN: Oh. shit.
(GROANING)
(ERNEST YELLS)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS. GRUNTING)
(NECK SNAPS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PANTING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
LEAD A CAPPELLA SINGER:
Push it back.
(A CAPPELLA SINGERS
SINGING)
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Excommunicado.
In effect. 10 minutes.
Let it be known the Bowery
will honor the Excommunicado.
No help.
no services of any kind.
Doc! Doc. it's Wick!
DOCTOR: Mr. Wick.
No. no. You shouldn't be here.
Hour's almost up.
I know. Doc. please.
There's still time.
No! I can't.
I still have five minutes!
Please.
(LOCKS TURNING)
Come on. Come on.
All right. sit there.
(GROANS)
All right. let me see.
Let me see.
Uh-huh.
Puncture wound.
Went deep.
Nicked the artery.
Here you go.
- (GRUNTS IN PAIN)
- (OBJECTS CLATTERING)
DOCTOR: All right.
(TICKING)
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Excommunicado.
In effect. one minute.
(TICKING CONTINUES)
Doc?
Yeah. We're halfway there.
- Five seconds.
- Yeah.
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Excommunicado.
In effect. in five. four...
- (TICKING)
- Three. two...
One.
(CLOCK TOLLING)
Sorry. Mr. Wick.
I know. Rules.
Ah. rules.
(TOLLING CONTINUES)
- (PHONES RINGING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OPERATOR: (ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. 14 million.
Open contract
is now in effect.
All services are suspended.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
And away we go.
(CELL PHONES RINGING)
(JOHN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SPITS)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
DOCTOR:
Top shelf. On the right.
Yeah. Take four.
It will give you energy.
Help with the pain.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
(SIGHS) Mr. Wick?
They'll never believe
I stopped on the hour.
But you did.
They'll know.
Know what?
I told you
where the medicine was.
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
- Where?
- Here.
Just below my floating rib.
Be sure not to hit
my large intestine.
(GROANS)
Oh. wait!
One may not be enough.
(COCKS GUN)
(GRUNTS)
Yeah. All right.
Be sure not to graze my...
Oh! (GROANING)
Good luck. Mr. Wick.
Thanks. Doc.
(DOCTOR GROANS)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (HORNS HONKING)
(BOTH SPEAKING MANDARIN)
- Its him.
- Yes. let's go.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(BOTH SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Open the door.
Shoot the lock.
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUN CHAMBER CLICKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BONES CRACK)
(GASPING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (PANTING)
(MAN COUGHING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (KNIFE CLATTERS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(HORNS HONKING)
(WHINES)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- Its him.
- Yes.
Tell them that he's arriving at the corner.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(HORSE HUFFS)
- (MAN SCREAMING)
- (HORSE NEIGHS)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(CAR HORN BLARING)
(ON SPEAKERS)
John Wick. Open contract.
Increase. 15 million.
Where are you going.
Jonathan?
We are closed.
(PANTING)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Look who it is.
And the belt.
Take him to her.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
See you later.
(BOTH SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Yes. yes.
(SLOW CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(DIRECTOR SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Again!
(BALLERINA PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Again!
(IN ENGLISH) Jardani.
Why have you come home?
You present this to me
like an answer.
I still have my ticket.
After all the chaos you've
caused for the last few weeks.
you think
your ticket is valid?
You forget
that the Ruska Roma
is bound by the High Table.
and the High Table
stands above all?
They could kill me
just for talking to you.
You honor me by bringing death
to my front door.
Oh. Jardani.
what has become of you?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
I am Jardani Jovonovich.
I am a child of the Belarus.
An orphan of your tribe.
You are bound to help me.
(IN ENGLISH) You are bound...
And I am owed.
Rooney. enough!
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Follow me.
(IN ENGLISH) "You are owed."
You are owed nothing. Jardani.
You know. when my pupils
first come here.
they wish for one thing.
A life free of suffering.
I try to dissuade them
from these childish notions.
but as you know.
art is pain.
Life is suffering.
Somehow.
you managed to get out.
But here you are.
back where you began.
All of this. for what?
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
For a dog?
It wasn't just a dog.
Bringing back old memories?
- (CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INSTRUCTOR SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Pirouette.
(INSTRUCTOR VOCALIZING)
Pirouette. pirouette.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
DIRECTOR: (IN ENGLISH) Sit.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Even if I wanted to.
I can't help you. Jardani.
The High Table
wants your life.
How can you fight the wind?
How can you smash
the mountains?
How can you bury the ocean?
How can you escape
from the light?
Of course.
you can go to the dark.
But they're in the dark. too.
So tell me. Jardani.
What do you really want?
Passage.
Where did you want to go?
Casablanca.
(SCOFFS)
The path to paradise
begins in hell.
So be it.
You hand me your ticket.
I will tear it.
If that's what
you really desire.
With this. Jardani.
your ticket is torn.
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
You can never come home again.
Take him to the lifeboat.
Do svidanya.
(DOOR OPENS)
JOHN: Do svidanya.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Welcome to the Continental.
How may I help you?
Sir. There is an Adjudicator
here to see you.
Very well. sir.
The manager is in the lounge.
WINSTON: I presume you're
here to discuss John Wick.
If that's so.
we can make this short.
I told him to walk away.
he declined to do so.
And that's the all of it.
Mr. Wick broke the rules.
Oh. yes.
And I haven't got the
slightest idea where he is...
You're mistaken.
I'm not here for Mr. Wick.
I'm here because Mr. Wick
broke the rules in this hotel.
- Hmm.
- The blood was spilt
on the grounds of
the Continental. Was it not?
Oh. yes.
As a matter of fact.
the body gets colder
within these very walls.
I'd like to see it.
Santino D'Antonio.
A newly instated member
of the High Table.
slain by Mr. Wick
while seeking sanctuary
in the Continental.
With a .45 ACP.
it appears.
I had no control
over Mr. Wick's actions.
And yet. he lives
because you deemed it so. yes?
Yes.
You have known Mr. Wick
for a great many years.
It might even be fair
to call you friends. yes?
Instead of stopping him.
instead of killing him.
you stood by
and let him walk away
after he shot Santino
D'Antonio in front of you.
I made him Excommunicado.
But not before you gave
him an hour to escape.
He broke the rules
in my hotel.
This is exactly the
problem. your hotel.
Where is your fealty?
I've been of service
for over 40 years.
Under the Table.
Serving the Table.
Everything is under the Table.
I understand
that you have your loyalties.
but this cannot be overlooked.
Let me be clear.
I am here to adjudge you.
You have one week
to get your affairs in order.
Excuse me?
At such time.
your successor will be named.
There are rules.
they are the only things
that separate us...
- From the animals.
- Yes.
You have seven days.
In the meantime. if you need any
assistance with your transition.
you may look for me
in room 217.
Enjoy your stay
at the Continental.
There's an Adjudicator
here to see you.
(BOWERY KING SIGHS)
(PIGEONS COOING)
Welcome to my Mission Control.
Brain stem of my operation.
The information super flyway.
From whence I control
the word on the street.
the way of the world.
With pigeons.
Yes. You see rats with wings.
but I see the Internet.
No IP addresses.
No digital footprint.
Can't track it. can't hack it.
can't trace it.
Can you get disease from it?
Well. I wouldn't recommend
that you eat one.
What the hell do you want?
I wanted to see
where it didn't happen.
Where what didn't happen?
Where you didn't kill
John Wick.
I've always been
under the impression
that contracts and
executing them was optional.
I have no problem
with John Wick.
And yet. you gave John
a seven-round Kimber 1911.
knowing that
he intended to use it
to stand against the Table.
Yes?
This Kimber 1911.
to be exact.
You gave John Wick
seven bullets.
the High Table
is giving you seven days.
Seven days for what. exactly?
To settle your affairs
and find a new home
for your birds.
In seven days.
you abdicate your throne.
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHING)
Oh. my dear.
Tell me. do you know what
the Bowery is. Adjudicator?
Do you know what happens
when I wave my hand?
No. there will be no replacement
for me on the throne.
Because I am the throne. baby.
I am the Bowery!
I am all that you deign
not to look at
when you walk
down the street at night.
The Bowery is mine.
Mine alone.
Do not make the mistake
of thinking
you exist outside
the rules. no men do.
You have seven days.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MAN SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
(GRUNTING)
- (SCREAMS)
- (MAN YELLING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
YASSIN: Enough!
I'm afraid our friend here
is off limits.
But he's Excommunicado.
It seems the manager
has granted him amnesty.
Mr. Jonathan.
would you be so kind
as to come with me?
(MAN GROANS)
Welcome to Casablanca.
Mr. Wick.
- Thanks.
- (LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
YASSIN: Mr. Jonathan.
it has been a long time
since our fine city
has been graced
with your presence.
I need to talk to...
Yes. Ms. Al-Azwar.
she's expecting you.
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
My. my. welcome
to the Moroccan Continental.
I hope you'll find it
to your taste.
Right this way.
Ms. Al-Azwar.
she waits for no man.
Best of luck. Mr. Jonathan.
Best of luck.
(CHUCKLING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MUFFLED CHATTER IN DISTANCE)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
WOMAN: You a dog person. John?
- (GUN COCKS)
- JOHN: Sofia?
(GROANS) Sofia!
You can't kill the bearer
of your marker.
I didn't kill you.
I just shot you.
Nice suit.
(BULLET CASING CLATTERS)
Good to see you. too.
I should shoot you
in the head right now.
I know.
Don't you do it.
You're Excommunicado. John.
And that marker
doesn't mean shit.
This is your blood.
Your bond.
When you needed help.
I was there.
Sit.
I was talking to you. John.
You do realize that
I'm management now. right?
I'm not service anymore. John.
So I don't go around
shooting people in the head.
I'm not asking you
to kill anyone.
I just need you
to get me to him.
- To who?
- Your old boss.
You want to kill Berrada.
I'm not gonna kill him.
I just need to talk.
What could he
possibly give to you?
(SIGHS)
Guidance.
Look. I made a deal when
I agreed to run this hotel.
And that deal said
that I had to follow
the rules of the Table.
If you're not gonna kill him.
he is gonna kill you.
and then probably me. too.
for walking you up in there.
If I make one mistake.
one enemy...
Maybe somebody goes
looking for my daughter.
And I know what you did.
John. to get her out.
But that's not a chance
I can take. Sorry.
Do you wanna know
where she is?
No. I don't ever wanna know.
Because I don't trust
that I won't go find her.
A part of me longs for her.
And I have to kill that part
of myself every day.
just to keep her safe.
Because sometimes you have
to kill what you love.
That's why I gave you that
marker in the first place.
That's why
I'm sitting here right now
and that's why I'm fucked!
- Consequences.
- Yeah.
Consequences.
I'm just asking you to try.
Either way. you and me.
we'll be even.
No.
After this.
we are less than even.
We leave in 10 minutes.
(DOG WHINES)
(J-POP SONG PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)
(MAN SPEAKING JAPANESE)
(MEN GREETING IN JAPANESE)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(IN ENGLISH)
How can I help you?
I wasn't expecting
the High Table so soon.
THE ADJUDICATOR:
There is a task.
It involves someone
who broke the rules
and stood against the Table.
John Wick. you mean.
My students
have not been idle.
John Wick and all
who've helped him.
You've heard the stories
about him. of course.
Killed scores of men this
past week alone because of...
A dog. a car.
I'm familiar.
And I'm interested.
Very.
Blowfish. Very fatal.
No soy.
I have served.
I will be of service.
(ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROANING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
- Stop!
- (MUSIC STOPS)
Out!
The High Table and the Ruska
Roma have an understanding.
Yes. and you helped John Wick.
He had a ticket.
But a ticket does not stand
above the Table.
Your penance
will be paid in blood.
Now...
Hold out your helping hands
and pledge your fealty.
I have served.
I will be of service.
(GASPS)
(DOG GROWLING)
We're not going in
like the old days.
It's just a conversation.
(SIGHS) Nothing's ever just
a conversation with you. John.
(DOG YAWNS)
Let's go.
(METAL CLANGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
BERRADA: Sofia.
Always so nice to see you.
And the dogs. of course. how marvelous.
May I pet one?
Certainly.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
(IN ENGLISH) Fantastic.
Jonathan Wick.
I had heard you had
made your way to our shores.
Come along now.
I am certain
we have much to discuss.
I must admit. I am curious.
What brings you to my domain?
Tell me.
Do you come here to kill me?
No.
Mr. Wick. do you know where
the word "assassin" comes from?
People argue. "Assassin."
Hashasheen.
followers of Hassan-i...
Eaters of hashish.
(CHUCKLES)
No. thank you.
But others contend
it comes from asasiyyun.
Meaning. "men who are faithful
"and who abide
by their beliefs."
You see that coin?
The first coin ever minted
in this facility.
Next to it. the first marker.
Not easy to track down.
believe me.
Now. this coin. of course.
it does not represent
monetary value.
It represents
the commerce of relationships.
a social contract in which
you agree to partake.
Order and rules.
You have broken the rules.
The High Table
has marked you for death.
Why would I allow you
to leave here alive.
when your life has been
by your own actions. forfeit?
I seek to make amends.
To pay for what I've done.
I seek a meeting with the one
who sits above the Table.
This dog.
I do so love it.
Tell me. does it shed
a great deal?
Occasionally.
When I leave. you can tell
the Elder I'm coming.
And if he wants me dead...
Then he will see to it that
your bones bleach under the sun.
I see.
And I would have provided him
with a choice.
I am sorry. Mr. Wick.
I cannot tell you
where to find the Elder.
You fail to understand.
The Elder
is not a man you find.
He can only choose
to find you.
You wish to speak with him?
Go to the edge of the
desert. look up.
Canis Minor.
the dog that followed Orion
through the sky.
You follow the brightest star.
Walk until
you are almost dead.
Then. keep walking.
When you are
on your last breath.
he will find you...
Or he will not.
I am grateful.
Thank you. sir.
Perhaps you were
not listening before.
The social contract.
The commerce of relationships.
You have received
a great gift.
I have hosted your friend.
What do you offer in return?
So soft and yet so fierce.
I love it. this dog.
I will keep it.
Excuse me?
This will be my gift.
This will be how
you show me your fealty.
No.
Surely it's the least
you can do.
No. you cannot keep my dog.
Very well.
Then I will kill it.
- (DOG YELPS)
- (SOFIA SCREAMS)
- (DOG WHINING)
- (SPEAKING ARABIC)
BERRADA: I'm sorry. Sofia.
This was for you to learn.
(WHINING)
Don't.
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (BARKING)
- (SCREAMING)
(BARKING)
(SCREAMING)
(BERRADA SCREAMING)
Sofia. Don't.
(SCREAMING)
He shot my dog.
I get it.
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
SOFIA: We gotta go. Now.
(MEN CLAMORING)
(GUNFIRE)
- (MEN SHOUTING)
- (DOGS BARKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (SHOUTS)
- (BARKING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (GUNSHOT)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
- (MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(BARKING)
(GRUNTING)
(SOFIA GRUNTING)
(MAN YELLS)
(DOGS SNARLING)
(MAN SHOUTING IN ARABIC)
- (BARKING)
- (SCREAMING)
(DOGS SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE)
(SHOUTS)
(SCREAMS)
(DOGS SNARLING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SNARLING)
(SCREAMS)
(SOFIA GRUNTING)
(GUNS CLICKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
- (SHOUTS)
- (SNARLING)
(SNARLING)
(GUNFIRE STOPS)
(SOFIA PANTING)
- (SHOUTS)
- (DOGS BARKING)
(PRAYER CHANTING ON SPEAKERS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(DOGS BARKING)
- (DOGS SNARLING)
- (MEN SCREAMING)
(SHOUTS.
BANGS ON CAR DOOR)
(DOGS BARKING)
(GRUNTS)
Here you go.
You're gonna die. John.
Whether out here
in this desert.
or somewhere else
down the road.
But you are gonna die.
Consequences.
(SPITS)
Better get going.
Sofia.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
Okay.
(PIGEON COOING)
You made your point.
You have earned my fealty.
Matter of fact...
I'm gonna shove so
much fealty up your ass
it's gonna come
spilling out of your mouth.
You had your chance.
Well. since you see it
that way.
I guess it's time I told you
to climb down off your High
Table and go fuck yourself.
Duly noted.
You gave John Wick
seven bullets.
your penance will be paid
with seven cuts.
Well. sometimes you gotta
cut a motherfucker.
Avert your eyes.
my sweet.
The king is dead.
Long live the king.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(CAMEL GRUNTING)
THE ELDER: Drink.
Don't worry. your weapon
is still there. Please drink.
My son. how have you
come to be so lost?
JOHN: Not lost.
Looking for you.
THE ELDER: You think
I speak of your location?
Never seen a man fight so hard
to end up
back where he started.
So tell me. Jonathan.
Why do you wish to live?
My wife. Helen.
To remember her.
To remember us.
So you seek to live
for the memory of love?
At least a chance to earn it.
I can give you one last chance
to earn a life.
However. it might not be
the life that you wish.
Complete a task for us.
and your Excommunicado
will be reversed.
The open contract closed.
you would be permitted
to continue to live.
Not free under the Table.
but bound to it.
Doing what you do best
for the rest of your days.
The choice is yours.
Die here and now.
Or continue to live
and remember through death.
What must be done?
The cost of your life
will be the death of others.
The first of which will be
the man they call Winston.
What?
He has forgotten his fealty.
Neither the open contract
nor the Excommunicado
will be lifted
until you complete your task.
So if you wish to live.
and if you wish to remember.
this is the choice
you must make.
I will serve.
I will be of service.
Very well. my son.
Cast aside your weakness
and reaffirm your fealty
to the table.
Mr. John Wick.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
I want to see. Show me.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
THE ELDER: (IN ENGLISH)
Thank you.
I accept this offering
and your fealty.
(JOHN GRUNTS IN PAIN)
(GROANS LOUDLY)
I wish you good luck
on your path.
Zahir will help you prepare
for your departure.
And Mr. Wick.
(SPEAKING ARABIC)
Welcome back.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA) JFK Express
now arriving on platform nine.
JFK Express now arriving
on platform nine.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
(BLADES STABBING)
TEACHER: Stick together. kids.
Make sure
you're holding the hand
of the person
in front and behind you.
You see? That's why
you're special. John Wick.
I wouldn't have stopped.
It's good to have you back.
How was your trip?
Going to the Continental?
He with you?
- (BODY THUDS)
- He was.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT
ON PA)
Nice trick.
(CELL PHONES RINGING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(BLADES UNSHEATHING)
(GRUNTING)
(BIKER SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(ENGINES REVVING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BIKER SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Sir! Put your weapon down.
ZERO: He's Excommunicado.
Unless you wish
to become the same.
I suggest you lower your gun.
(PANTING)
I'd like to see the manager.
Of course.
If you would be so kind
as to follow me.
- (SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
- (LOW CHATTER)
Please take a seat.
I will let him know
you have arrived.
(JOHN SIGHS)
I gotta tell you.
I've been looking forward to
meeting you for a long time.
I'm a huge fan. John Wick.
(CHUCKLES)
And so far.
you haven't disappointed.
Is that the dog?
He likes you.
Me? I'm more of
a cat person myself.
Hey. dog.
We're the same. you know.
Both given the same gift.
We're not the same.
Yes. we are.
No. we're not.
The manager
is ready for you now.
In the administrative lounge.
sir.
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
We're both masters of death.
Mr. Wick.
(DOG PANTING)
Sit.
Stay.
Good dog.
(DOG WHINES)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Tread carefully. Jonathan.
We only use this room
on special occasions.
When you simply have to see
what your opponent is holding
under the table.
(CHUCKLES)
How was your journey here?
Eventful?
Yeah.
Well. of course.
They sent men to kill you.
and now you to kill me.
Isn't that why you're here?
I have served.
I will be of service.
But you're having doubts.
Just don't make the mistake of
pretending this is personal.
If you feel you must.
put a bullet through my heart.
The High Table has asked me
to step down.
The hour?
The hour.
You should have killed me
in the Continental.
Maybe I should have.
Rules and consequences.
WINSTON: Hmm.
It seems like everyone
is suffering
from the consequences
of their actions.
And you're not stepping down?
No.
I don't think I am.
So it's war?
You're going to war
with the High Table?
Skirmish.
Unless you decide to shoot me.
But. then. I'd rather die
at the hand of a friend
than that of an enemy.
No. I've made my choice.
It's up to you to make yours.
What choice?
You shoot me.
you sell your soul.
But I'll be alive.
And I can remember her.
Until you die as a servant
of the High Table.
Now. you did the impossible.
you stopped. you got out.
You only came back because
Helen was taken away from you.
The real question is.
who do you wish to die as?
The Baba Yaga?
The last thing
many men ever see?
Or as a man who loved
and was loved by his wife?
Who do you wish
to die as. Jonathan?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Mr. Wick.
it's a pleasure to meet you.
I am an Adjudicator.
Have you decided to step down?
I think not.
And you? Will you be putting
a bullet in his head?
No. I don't think I will.
Very well.
(LINE RINGING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (PHONE RINGING)
Administration.
THE ADJUDICATOR: I'd like to
change a designation.
Verification?
Adjudication 1-0-1-1-9-7-9.
The Continental Hotel.
New York.
ADMINISTRATOR:
New designation?
Deconsecrated.
Processing.
(ON SPEAKERS) Administrator.
File. The New York
Continental Hotel.
The New York Continental Hotel
has been deconsecrated. Goodbye.
Gentlemen. this institution
is now deconsecrated.
Business may now be conducted
on Continental grounds.
Since you are refusing
to step down
and you are refusing a direct
order. your lives are now forfeit.
High Table emissaries will be
joining you presently
to see the removal of
your souls from the property.
Good evening. gentlemen.
This haven is safe no more.
Are services
still off limits to me?
Under the circumstances.
your privileges
are reinstated immediately.
What do you need?
Guns. Lots of guns.
(TRILLING)
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
Let's make a withdrawal.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (PHONES RINGING)
CHARON: Remember. sir.
These will be
High Table forces.
We may have to consider
our choices carefully.
Why?
Much has changed
during your time away.
Like what?
Well. let us say they have
made armor improvements.
May I suggest
the 2011 Combat Master
in combination with
the nine millimeter major.
(PHONE RINGING)
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Attention. all guests.
The Continental Hotel
is closing for fumigation.
We apologize
for the inconvenience.
Please make your way
to the nearest exit.
Attention. all guests.
The Continental Hotel...
It seems circumstances
have changed in your favor.
Your transaction
may now be conducted
on Continental grounds.
We'll be sending some of our
finest for additional support.
Cool. Very cool.
(GUN CLICKS)
125 grain.
1.425 feet per second.
Serious business.
Thank you.
Let us begin.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC CONTINUES IN DISTANCE)
(EXPLOSIONS IN DISTANCE)
Charon. would you help set
the mood for our new guests?
Of course. sir.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
I know you'll do
the Continental proud.
I'll see you soon. sir.
And you. Jonathan.
do what you do best.
What's that?
Hunt.
(SPEAKING LATIN)
If you want peace...
Prepare for war.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(MAN 1 SCREAMS)
(MAN 2 COUGHS)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(GUNFIRE)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(JOHN YELLING)
Winston! Winston!
(GRUNTS)
I need more firepower.
(ORCHESTRAL MUSIC
CONTINUES PLAYING)
Armor improvements.
12-gauge steel slugs.
Armor-piercing.
- (BEEPS)
- (WHIRRING)
(GUNSHOT)
(MAN SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
(MEN GROAN)
(MAN YELLS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
(MAN GRUNTING)
(BULLETS CLATTERING)
(GUN CLICKING)
(MUFFLED GUNSHOTS)
(FIRING GUN)
- (BLADE SLASHES)
- (GROANS)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
No one kills you but me.
(IN ENGLISH)
Only by my sword. John.
(GRUNTS)
(PHONE RINGING)
THE ADJUDICATOR: I know you
believe you can keep this up.
But I assure you...
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(BULLET CASINGS CLATTERING)
(CLANGING)
(YELLING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
(CLAPPING)
(MAN YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BOTH SPEAKING INDONESIAN)
Pleased to meet you. Mr. Wick.
It's an honor to fight with you. Mr. Wick.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
He is getting slow.
He is been retired for 5 years.
But he is still... John Wick.
We will see.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(JOHN SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
(GLASS CRACKS)
(SPEAKING INDONESIAN)
Be seeing you.
(IN ENGLISH)
John. you're incredible.
Exhausted.
outnumbered...
Obviously in pain.
And you still beat
all of my students.
If I didn't
have to kill you.
we'd be pals.
Let's do this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
See? We're the same.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
- (BONE CRACKS)
- (ZERO YELLS)
(PANTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BONE CRACKS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GROANS)
(YELLS AND GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(GROANS)
(LINE RINGING)
(PHONE RINGING)
I would like to suggest
a parley.
A parley would be good.
Very well.
Are we in play. sir?
Oh. very much so.
(JOHN PANTING)
(ZERO GROANING)
(ZERO CHOKES)
Hey. John.
That was
a pretty good fight. huh?
Yeah.
(JOHN GRUNTS)
ZERO: Yeah.
Don't worry about me. John.
I just gotta catch my breath.
I'll catch up to you. John.
No. you won't.
(GRUNTS)
THE ADJUDICATOR:
You gentlemen. of course.
realize that was
the first wave.
Merely an amuse-bouche.
We can keep this up
as long as you'd like.
but it only ends one way.
Are you sure a protracted war
is the best way forward?
There won't be anything
"protracted" about it.
Oh. you can take
the Continental.
I have no doubt about that.
But keeping it. that's
a different matter entirely.
My allegiances run
way beyond this building.
We are High Table.
And we
are New York City.
- Are we negotiating?
- (DOOR OPENS)
Hmm.
I believe we are.
Parley?
WINSTON: Parley.
THE ADJUDICATOR:
What do you propose we do?
Let me keep my power.
Under the Table.
WINSTON: I have served
and been a beacon
of order and stability
to our industry
for over 40 years.
Now. I humbly acknowledge
I overstepped
and re-pledge my fealty
to the High Table.
Winston.
THE ADJUDICATOR: You were
merely showing strength
so we would let you
keep the Continental.
The High Table
accepts your fealty.
But what about him?
What are we going to do
about John Wick?
Oh. he has to die.
- Sorry. Jonathan.
- (GROANS) Winston!
Don't see any other way.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (JOHN GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Very well. gentlemen.
The Continental will now
be reconsecrated.
Good day to you both.
Well played. sir.
(METAL CLINKING)
How long do you estimate
until we reopen?
Oh. should be no time at all.
Mr. Wick is gone.
A true tragedy.
You misunderstand.
I mean that he is no longer
on the street.
That seems improbable.
And yet. true.
(WHIMPERS)
I trust you understand the
repercussions if he survives.
Both from above and below.
The last thing
either one of us needs
is Mr. Wick paying us
a visit in the night.
For both our sakes.
I'll hope you see to it
that this situation
is taken care of. yes?
Absolutely.
How far can he get?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Baba Yaga.
(WHEELS SQUEAKING)
BOWERY KING: Mmm.
(WHIMPERS)
(GROANS)
BOWERY KING:
How you doing. John?
You look as bad as I feel.
(CHUCKLES)
Johnny. Johnny. Johnny.
Raise a hand
if you can hear me. John.
Oh. shit.
They took a finger.
Ain't that a bitch?
(CHUCKLING)
(LAUGHS AND GROANS)
Oh. John fucking Wick.
So. the old boy
keeps his hotel
and you take the fall.
Can't say I blame him.
I would've done the same thing
if I was in his shoes.
But this High Table shit...
Seven cuts.
(CHUCKLES)
Under the Table
is where shit gets done.
And they're about to find out.
if you cut a king.
you better cut him
to the quick.
(SIGHS)
So...
Let me ask you. John.
How do you feel?
'Cause I am really pissed off.
You pissed. John?
Hmm?
Are you?
(GROANS)
Yeah.
Subtitles by explosiveskull & EVO
Sync by GoldenBeard
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm